Summary

RF Electrical Engineer II with 2.5 years experience in RF circuit design and analysis, leadership experience, research, and project management. Experience working in Agile CCA build environment. Looking to get more experience in the field of software engineering.

Education

Master of Science in Engineering, Electrical Engineering	May 2018
Bachelor of Science in Engineering, Electrical Engineering	May 2017
Barrett, the Honors College	
Arizona State University, Tempe, Arizona	GPA: 3.95

Arizona State University, Tempe, Arizona

Relevant Coursework

♦ Python for Engineers	♦ UX/UI Design
♦ Numerical Methods using MATLAB	♦ Hardware Design Language Programming Logic (VHDL)
♦ C++, Intro to Programming	♦ Data Mining & Machine Learning

Professional Skills

1 Totostonar omno					
<u>Technical</u>		<u>Lab</u>			
♦ Python	♦ LabVIEW	♦ RF Test & Automation	♦ Microsoft Excel (Pivot Tables)		
♦ C++/MATLAB	♦ Machine Learning	♦ Oscilloscope	♦ Reports and Presentations		
♦ JavaScript, HTML, CSS	♦ PostgreSQL	♦ Soldering	♦ Data Analysis		
♦ VBA	♦ GitHub	♦ CCA Design and Fabrication	♦ Failure Analysis		

Work Experience

Raytheon, Tucson, Arizona

June 2018 – Present

RF Electrical Engineer II

- ▶ Designed and wrote testing automation scripts in LabVIEW.
- ▶ Wrote VBA script to find discrepancies in EDM data.
- ► Facilitated system level design of RF circuit cards.
- ▶ Designed etched components and performed RF analysis using HFSS.

General Dynamics, Scottsdale, Arizona

Aug 2017 – April 2018

May 2017 - Aug 2017

RF Engineering Intern

- ▶ Bread boarding RF components for failure analysis and characterization.
- ▶ Used HFSS to design and simulate divider, coupler, filter, and connector transitions.

Raytheon, Tucson, Arizona

Graduate RF Engineering Intern

- ► Assisted in design and implementation of RF filters.
- ▶ Used HFSS Statistical Analysis to run Monte Carlo on filters.
- ▶ Performed RF testing for system performance and derated components for review.

Projects

Time-Series Forecasting using LSTM Networks and Prophet

Python for Engineers – Final Deliverable (available upon request)

- ▶ Used python and machine learning to compare forecasting algorithms: LSTM & Prophet.
- ▶ Developed novel method for LSTM model to predict upon its previous predicted value (forecast).

Simulating Effects of Probe Placement on Calibration Accuracy using TRL

Millimeter Wave & THz Measurements – Final Deliverable (available upon request)

- ▶ Used HFSS to model calibration standards for thru, reflect, load (TRL).
- ▶ Used Python to introduce error (Gaussian noise) simulating probe placement error and plot results.
- ► Successfully showed percent error increases exponentially as a function of probe displacement.

RFID Lock using MSP4332P401R and TRF7970A Booster Pack

Texas Instruments Internship Design Challenge

- ▶ Used C++ to develop state machine for RFID Lock.
- ▶ Discovered bug in TI firmware release and showed failure mode in RFID reader.

Ultra-Smart-Brain Full Stack Web App

Udemy Web Development Course Project - https://ultra-smart-brain-redux.herokuapp.com/

- ▶ Used React and Redux to make face recognition application using Clarifai's API.
- ► Created a database using PostgreSQL to store user information and stats.